<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Deploying Microservices to EKS Fargate on Amazon EKS Roadshow</title>
    <link>//localhost:57086/beginner/180_fargate/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Deploying Microservices to EKS Fargate on Amazon EKS Roadshow</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2019 00:00:00 -0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="//localhost:57086/beginner/180_fargate/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Creating a Fargate Profile</title>
      <link>//localhost:57086/beginner/180_fargate/creating-profile/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2019 00:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:57086/beginner/180_fargate/creating-profile/</guid>
      <description>The Fargate profile allows an administrator to declare which pods run on Fargate. Each profile can have up to five selectors that contain a namespace and optional labels. You must define a namespace for every selector. The label field consists of multiple optional key-value pairs. Pods that match a selector (by matching a namespace for the selector and all of the labels specified in the selector) are scheduled on Fargate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deploy an application to Fargate</title>
      <link>//localhost:57086/beginner/180_fargate/fargate-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 13:36:57 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:57086/beginner/180_fargate/fargate-app/</guid>
      <description>Deploy a simple application to Fargate: Create a Kubernetes Namespace game-2048
cat &amp;lt;&amp;lt; EOF &amp;gt; f-app-namespace.yaml apiVersion: v1 kind: Namespace metadata: name: game-2048 EOF kubectl apply -f f-app-namespace.yaml namespace/game-2048 created  Our fargate profile is matched to the namespace game-2048.
Next create deployment that uses the game-2048 namespace:
Create a kubernetes deployment manifest using this command:
cat &amp;lt;&amp;lt; EOF &amp;gt; f-app-deployment.yaml apiVersion: apps/v1 kind: Deployment metadata: namespace: game-2048 name: fargate-deployment-2048 spec: selector: matchLabels: app.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clean Up</title>
      <link>//localhost:57086/beginner/180_fargate/cleaning/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2019 00:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:57086/beginner/180_fargate/cleaning/</guid>
      <description>Cleaning up To delete the resources used in this chapter:
Interrupt the port forwarding with ctrl-C
And delete the deployment:
kubectl delete -f app-deployment.yaml eksctl delete fargateprofile \  --name game-2048 \  --cluster eksworkshop-eksctl </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
