<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>operations on Amazon EKS Roadshow</title>
    <link>//localhost:50404/tags/operations/</link>
    <description>Recent content in operations on Amazon EKS Roadshow</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="//localhost:50404/tags/operations/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>EKS CloudWatch Container Insights</title>
      <link>//localhost:50404/beginner/250_cloudwatch_container_insights/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 15:27:17 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:50404/beginner/250_cloudwatch_container_insights/</guid>
      <description>In this chapter we will learn and leverage the new CloudWatch Container Insights to see how you can use native CloudWatch features to monitor your EKS Cluster performance.
You can use CloudWatch Container Insights to collect, aggregate, and summarize metrics and logs from your containerized applications and microservices. Container Insights is available for Amazon Elastic Container Service, Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service, and Kubernetes platforms on Amazon EC2. The metrics include utilization for resources such as CPU, memory, disk, and network.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Patching/Upgrading your EKS Cluster</title>
      <link>//localhost:50404/beginner/320_eks_upgrades/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:50404/beginner/320_eks_upgrades/</guid>
      <description>Patching/Upgrading your EKS Cluster As EKS tracks upstream Kubernetes that means that customers can, and should, regularly upgrade their EKS so as to stay within the project&amp;rsquo;s upstream support window. This used to be the current version and two version back (n-2) - but it was recently extended to three versions back (n-3).
There is a new major version of Kubernetes every quarter which means that the Kubernetes support window has now gone from three quarters of a year to one full year.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
